Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is a time known as
the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all, through all the trouble.
At times through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
This weather's perfect!
So which way is the
grand lot is it that way
or maybe this way that way over here maybe
there I don't know
where gonna be i want to
see this place i want
to see you need to sit
Jeez you bug me oh sorry
i'm just excited that we
finally got a cook on board
now we just need Nami!
Then nothing will stand
between us and the Grand Line!
Nami, I could just sit around all day
and think about how beautiful she is.
I can't wait till I get to see her again.
So, are we getting close to where Nami is?
You know, the island?
You're way too naive and way too young!
Don't you get it?
Don't you realize every second that passes
brings us closer to the infamous R-log?
Nami couldn't stop looking at
Arlong's picture when she saw it.
And it wasn't a normal kind of stare.
There was something different
about the way she was staring.
Something focused.
I'm telling you,
Nami's planning on taking down Arlong and
then collecting the 20
million berry bounty.
For all we know, while we just sit here,
she's already making her
way through his compound.
That's nice.
Let's eat.
Sounds good.
Ah!
Don't tell me you guys
are so clueless that you
have actually never
heard of the evil Arlong!
Uh, no. Nope.
Listen up, boys!
Time for your education on the
cunning shark that is Arlong.
Arlong is a fishman who used to destroy
everything in his path up
and down the Grand Line.
Fishman? That's cool.
I don't think I've ever
met one of those before.
I've heard that the females
on Fishman Island are some
of the most beautiful creatures
in the world to behold.
Fishman sounds weird.
Do they look like this?
Can't you focus for just one minute,
please all right I will start
from the very beginning the reason
they call the Grand Line of pirate
graveyard in the first place
Is because of our long and the
other two powers like him who rule
over it the first of the powers
are known as the seven warlords
Seven Warlords?
The Seven Warlords are pirates
authorized by the government. Seriously?
Why would any pirate on the
sea want government approval?
For protection.
The government looks the other way in
exchange for a cut of their treasure,
and they're allowed to exist.
Of course, to other pirates,
they're just government dogs.
But they didn't get to where
they are by being weak.
These guys are powerful.
The man who defeated Zoro
is one of these warlords.
His name is Hawkeye Mihawk.
That's so cool!
I can't wait to meet
all seven of these guys!
They sound awesome!
Yeah, well, the first among the warlords,
at least first you should know about?
is Jinbei, captain of the Fishmen.
He is dangerous like no
one you've ever known?
Easily causing as much
havoc and destruction!
around the Grand Line as Arlong.
Is this closer?
That looks just like your last
picture, only standing up.
Arlong has taken control of over 20
towns since coming to the East Blue.
His strength easily surpasses
anyone you've encountered,
including that of Don Crocus.
He's devastating.
So why do you think Nami would go
after this guy all by herself, huh?
I told you already.
She wants to collect
the bounty on his head.
Oh, wouldn't it be great
if Nami was a mermaid?
I'd give anything to see that.
She'd look like this.
Tear that thing up or die!
Have either of you morons heard a
single word that I've said to you?
Sure, badass fish man.
Some guy's stronger than some other guy.
We get it.
No, you don't get it.
You've never had to face a fish man.
Well, we will when we get
there, so don't worry about it.
I guess I'll get lunch started.
About time. Let's eat. What? Food?
What are you in the mood for?
I want meat right off the bone!
I want salty bean sprouts!
Okay, leave it to me.
This won't take long.
Meat and bean sprouts, no problem.
Man, having a cook is the best! Huh? Huh?
It sure is!
Bring me meat!
Lots of meat! Sprouts!
I want bean sprouts!
Here's this month's take.
I hope you enjoy it.
Ah, Arlong, you are so much smarter than
your regular run-of-the-mill pirate.
You know how the world works.
Likewise,
there aren't many marine captains
who know that befriending
me means they can milk the
East Blue for eternity.
The fact that you understand makes you more
like me than any other marine out here.
Thank you very much.
Don't thank me. Thank money.
It's the only thing you
can count on in this world.
It's more reliable than
people, that's for sure.
Don't you agree?
Of course.
As a rule, I hate all humans.
But you are the one tolerable
exception that I found.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Why not stay a while and
have a drink with me?
I would, but the longer a marine
cruiser stays docked at a pirate island,
the quicker we get unwanted attention.
I'll kill anyone who reports you.
Everybody knows that.
Thank you, but still, we must go. Hey!
The captain is leaving.
Escort him back to his ship.
Yes, sir!
The pot's back that
way. Hop in. Thank you.
That's very kind of you.
When I see your face, it
always makes me want to laugh.
It's funny.
You look like a rat.
Hey, Hachi, watch your mouth now.
The captain's our honored guest.
Oh, right.
Sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
Here we go, man.
These fishmen are disgusting.
Such a vile group, but
they sure do pay well.
Hey, you!
Get out of my way!
Arlong's going to die today!
He killed my daddy, and so now
I'm going to have to kill him!
So move, or I'll have to kill you too!
Hey!
Now,
you should know that
Arlong doesn't have time
to deal with whimpering
little punks like you.
You're too young. Go home.
Take that with you and use it to
keep yourself out of trouble, kid.
Go to hell!
Nami, you've returned.
I haven't seen you around
here for quite a while.
So, how did you do this time?
Who are you talking to?
You know, I can't believe the world
is full of such blind idiots, modesty.
You girl are one excellent
liar. That's true.
Listen up, everybody!
Nami's finally returned!
Time for a party!
All right, we're here.
That's Arlong Park ahead.
Arlong Park, huh?
So this is the hideout of Arlong the
Fishman Pirate from the Grand Line?
I hope Nomi's really here.
Big Sis-Nami's ship was the Going
Mary, so before we do anything stupid,
we should quietly check to see if
it stopped on this island first.
Yeah, good idea.
Let's attack.
But I just said we shouldn't
do anything stupid!
What?
Attack, you idiot!
We know nothing about this place!
Yeah, these guys are the fishmen!
We need some kind of plan to do that!
While the two of you are busy
blabbering and wimping out,
I'm placing my thoughts on the
battle we're about to face.
Luffy told me to bring her
back and I'll do just that.
Let's go!
There it is!
Ha! Found it! The Going Mary!
It's right over there!
Then she has to be on
the island somewhere.
We just have to find her.
What do you think you're doing?
Would you idiots untie me?
I am not the enemy!
We're east of Arlong Park
here at Cocoyashi Village.
But it's strange.
Why would she have stopped
so far from the village?
Untie me, dammit!
Zoro, you're hurt way too bad to
be of any help when we go ashore.
Just sit tight and relax.
It's okay.
Rista, you can help next time.
One of these days, I'm going to
skewer him like a piece of meat.
Fear not, gentlemen.
I will bring back the girls safely.
Looks like skipping Arlong
Park has sure cheered you up.
Prepare the anchor.
Bring us alongside the Going Merry.
Aye.
Ah, yes.
Now that we're underway, it's time
to give a name to this voyage.
I think I shall call it the Great
Adventures of Captain Usopp.
What is it?
What'd you see?
It's fishmen!
Full speed ahead!
Okie Dock.
Why didn't we just dock right there?
Didn't you see that?
There were three fishmen over there!
It's Arlong's crew!
We can't stop here right now!
Do not yell at me!
If there are fishmen here, this entire
area must be under Arlong's control,
so what now?
We could just say we couldn't find her.
Untie me now, morons! Come on!
Never seen that boat before. Suspicious.
Let's run!
Okay, untie me! Damn it!
Fight!
Hey!
You two get back here or you're gonna die!
There's just this one guy.
Maybe he just drifted here
from real far out or something.
Yeah, right.
Those guys are dead and
they don't even know it.
Maybe somebody just wanted
him to die real slowly.
I think we should take him to our law.
Forgive me, Zoro.
I will tell Luffy that you were
courageous to the bitter end.
Please forgive me, Zoro.
I'll never forget you.
Okay, now let's find some land. Right.
I think this place is called Gosa Village.
What happened here?
I heard Arlong came through here a few
weeks back, but I never thought that...
Everything's upside down.
I've heard people say that
fishmen can be stronger
than normal human beings
by a very wide margin.
I guess this is how strong you have
to be to survive the Grand Line.
Maybe, but even the street's upside down.
The monster Mama caused
this destruction. Monster?
Don't tell me this place has monsters.
We caught him out on the Grand Line
and brought him back here with us.
From the Grand Line, huh?
Wait. We...
You!
You were with that guy from the boat!
Later!
Come back here!
That was close.
I wish you luck.
I'll just hold my position here and wait
for our backup from Yosaku and Luffy.
You may be a fish man, but there's
no way you can catch me on dry land.
I'm a very fast runner.
I'm a beautiful gazelle.
What the heck?
Got you, stupid fish man.
And now I'll avenge my
father by killing you.
Honestly, how many times
do I have to tell you,
Koby, you do not mess with the fish men.
It was just one person who
decided to stand up to them
and they responded by
slaughtering everyone in Koza.
Hm, you look and smell just like a fish
man, but I can see that you're human,
mostly human. Not mostly!
Where'd you go? Over here?
Crap!
A fish man!
And this time it's for real.
All right, stand back and
let me handle this one.
Watch as Captain Usa
takes out this fish man
Take this.
It's my special attack. Let's starve!
I guess he wasn't
listening when I said the
fishmen would kill us
if we messed with them.
Come on, tough guy.
Where am i my house
sleep well who are you
i'm no Chaka i grow
tangerines here want one?
That's right you're the one that hit me on
the head just when i was gonna save you!
I'm the one who saved you.
If you had actually gone
through with attacking that fish
man You would have been killed
for sure stupid outsider!
You'd figure a kid from here
would already know better?
What would make a child
do something so reckless?
That's a question I'd
really like an answer for.
I know, I know, but they killed my daddy.
They took everything from me.
Those fishmen destroyed our
town, killed my friends.
I had to make them pay for
what they did, no matter what!
Don't you get that?
So I went to Arlong Park by myself.
But this girl stopped me from going in.
She's like an evil witch.
I can't stand this, I
have to avenge my father!
I don't care if I die.
Then die.
If you're truly prepared to die, then go!
But you had better understand, boy.
I stopped you.
And this witch you hate kept you
from carrying out your revenge.
So far, you've cheated death twice.
Just finish your tea and go.
Hey, you're being a little
rough on him, don't you think?
I don't care who he is.
If he wants to kill
himself, then so be it!
He doesn't have what it
takes to suffer for revenge.
What?
It takes time.
I suffer as well.
Revenge is not an easy
path for one to carve out.
And to die just because you're too foolish
for patience is nothing
but a coward's plan.
What do you want from me?
I can't stand the way I feel, but...
How's your mom?
She's alive.
Then go back home.
She's worried about you.
For a chick with tattoos,
you're actually really sweet.
Piss off.
It's time you told me why you
decided to come here to our village.
Oh, right.
My name is Captain Usopp.
I'm looking for a girl named Nami.
No way!
She's a part of the Arlong crew!
It certainly looks that way.
Everybody here knows that cow.
Even the little boy.
It gets better, though.
That cow is my sister.
We grew up here.
Well, technically, she's my adopted
sister since we were both orphans.
But a sister's a sister,
you know what I mean?
I don't believe it!
Uh, Nami's house?
It's mine, too.
We were raised together in this house.
She's the closest thing to family I
have left since our foster mother died.
The three of us used to be so happy
together in Cocoyashi Village.
So, you're telling me that Nami
betrayed her mother, her sister,
and her whole village just to
be a part of Arlong's crew?
Yeah, pretty much.
A real witch, huh?
Damn, Nami is a total witch.
She had us completely
fooled the entire time.
To think she was just after
the treasure for herself.
Even after she risked her
life to save my village.
I don't understand.
She seemed so happy with us. Yeah?
She was happy?
Huh.
My sister.
We came here to try to convince
her to come back with us.
But I guess now that's pointless.
I just remembered that
a shipmate of mine was
taken prisoner by the
fishman before we got here.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I hope he's okay.
I hope he's at least not dead.
Open the gates!
We have a prisoner on board this vessel!
One more time, what was your purpose
in coming here to this island?
Like I said before, I'm looking
for a girl, you half-fish bastard
Wow,
for someone I consider a good meal
You are either really stupid or
you've got a lot of guts in there
We fishmen are simply the next rung
up the evolutionary ladder from you
pathetic humans We are incredibly
resilient We can breathe both on
land and underwater An ability which
clearly establishes our physical
superiority over you I don't know
if this will make any sense to that
puny brain rolling around in your
head But fishmen are the lords of
all creatures And to fight against
us is to defy nature I'm really sick
of listening to your big ideas, Arlong
Why are you always so serious, Nami?
You know that I wasn't talking about you.
You are a very special human,
our greatest navigator, and
a valued member of this crew.
You always have been.
Say what you will, but I'm a
lot smarter than any of you.
That's for sure.
Why did he call you his navigator, Nami?
You can't honestly expect me
to believe you work for him.
Hold on, is this guy a
friend of yours, Nami?
Don't be ridiculous.
This is just another fool
who thought I wasn't gonna
steal all of his treasure
right out from under his nose!
To think he actually followed
me here without knowing that!
Shows how stupid he is so this is
the person you really are all along?
I thought you couldn't stand
pirates you thought wrong.
It was all an act and
you bought the whole show
That's
I'm a pirate, plain and simple,
and a navigator for Arlong.
She had you guys completely fooled.
It's no use.
She's cold-blooded.
She betrayed her family for money,
so you really shouldn't feel too bad.
If I were you, I would just admit defeat
and try to forget the day you met her.
I don't need to.
Because I never saw anything in her
to be trusted in the first place.
If she turned out to be a serial
killer, I wouldn't be surprised.
Fine, then why don't you just
get the hell out of here?
I'm tired of your face.
Hey, anybody know why that
guy just jumped in the water?
It looks to me like he was just
trying to get away from Nami.
I don't blame him.
She can be really mean sometimes.
Maybe he's trying to escape any of you.
His arms and legs tied up?
I gotta say, that looked a lot
more like a suicide attempt.
To me, leave him.
That idiot!
They're back up she saved him.
What do you think you're doing?
No, what do you think you're doing?
You're really just a nice girl
who can't watch one guy die.
Why don't you quit
pretending and you might
want to jump my little cricker next time?
I thought it was dead.
Oh, you bastard!
Try that again and I'll make sure you die.
Really?
That's a lot of bandages.
You must have been hurt pretty bad.
Actually, I forgot my shirt.
Grabbed these to cover up so
you wouldn't get distracted.
Tell
me what?
Should we do with this guy?
Lock him up.
I'll take care of him.
when I have the time.
Arlong!
Hey, Arlong!
Yeah?
Well, spit it out. What is it? Yes, sir.
This guy didn't come here alone.
There was another long-nosed, weird-looking
guy with him, but he got away.
What the hell, Usaba?
You left me for dead
and got spotted anyway?
I think...
I think he escaped into Cocoyashi Village.
Cocoyashi, huh?
That's perfect.
Now I have two reasons to go.
Hey!
Arlong's coming!
He is?
But why?
We just paid him this
month's tribute, didn't we?
It's probably about my
weapons cache they found.
Everyone go home.
Genzo.
They're here!
So you're the fool who thought he
could hoard weapons on my island?
That's me, I'm a collector.
Is there a new law that forbids us
from having hobbies now as well?
Next you'll be telling us that we can't
read books or play with
our children anymore?
No, hobbies are fine.
It would be weapons that I have forbidden.
They make it difficult for me
and my men to keep the peace!
That's him?
Our lung's gigantic!
He's not even human!
Nope, he's a fish man. For real?
I'm responsible for 20 towns and
villages, including this one.
And as your leader, I cannot tolerate
even a little rebelliousness.
Wiping out Gosa was just
a small example of what
can happen when you do
not do as you are told.
Tribute money must be paid no
matter what. What? Tribute money?
It's just what it sounds like, money
we pay him so we can stay alive.
Adults and children, if there is
even a single person who can't pay?
Then what happened to Gosa will happen
to everyone in this village as well!
Our town and the people in it
will be wiped from existence.
He destroyed an entire
town because of one person?
That's how Arlong rules.
To them we're nothing but a subspecies,
so killing us has always been easy.
You pathetic humans need to stop
with all this thinking you're up to.
It's your greatest weakness.
I'm allowing you to
contribute to greatness here.
Soon, Fistman will conquer the humans,
and your tributes will be a small part of
the beginning of the
glorious Arlong Empire!
Arlong Empire?
They're planning on taking
over the entire East Blue!
Get out of here quick.
Arlong's gonna be back soon.
I began to wonder what could be
the reason it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true!
It's because of you.
Show me how to catch those feelings,
get them to come back to me?
I'll do what I must be, cause
they're everything I want to be.
Pass these arms around my dreams
and pull up back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way!